Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records, 1918-2018.
New York State College of Agriculture 4-H club records
- Series V. Photographs
  - G. Fairs and Field Days
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 78)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 79)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 1)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 2)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 4)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 5)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 6)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 7)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 8)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 9)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 10)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 11)
    - Field Days at Cornell, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 12)
    - Field Days at Cornell- demonstrations, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 13)
    - Field Days at Cornell- demonstrations, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 14)
    - Field Day groups- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 15)
    - Field Day groups- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 16)
    - Field Day groups- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 17)
    - Field Day groups- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 18)
    - Cornell scenes (Box 140, Folder 19)
    - Garden day- Sidney, New York, 1932,1934 (Box 140, Folder 20)
    - Rallies- various counties, 1934-1936 (Box 140, Folder 21)
    - Rallies and parades, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 23)
    - Camp Pyrke, 1939 (Box 140, Folder 24)
    - State Fair- Fenner studios (Box 140, Folder 25)
    - State Fair (Box 140, Folder 26)
    - State Fair (Box 140, Folder 27)
    - State Fair (Box 140, Folder 28)
    - State Fair, 1919 (Box 140, Folder 29)
    - State Fair, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 30)
    - State Fair, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 31)
    - State Fair, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 32)
    - State Fair, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 33)
    - State Fair, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 34)
    - State Fair, 1921 (Box 140, Folder 35)
    - State Fair, 1922 (Box 140, Folder 36)
    - State Fair, 1922 (Box 140, Folder 37)
    - State Fair, 1922 (Box 140, Folder 38)
    - State Fair, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 39)
    - State Fair, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 40)
    - State Fair, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 41)
    - State Fair, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 42)
    - State Fair, 1923 (Box 140, Folder 43)
    - State Fair, 1924 (Box 140, Folder 44)
    - State Fair, 1924 (Box 140, Folder 45)
    - State Fair, 1924 (Box 140, Folder 46)
    - State Fair, 1925 (Box 140, Folder 47)
    - State Fair, 1930,1931 (Box 140, Folder 48)
    - State Fair, 1935 (Box 140, Folder 49)
    - State Fair- 4-H club costume revue, 1936 (Box 140, Folder 50)
    - State Fair, 1937 (Box 140, Folder 51)
    - State Fair, 1942 (Box 140, Folder 52)
    - State and county fairs, 1997-2000 (Box 147)
    - State Fair, 2005; CD-3889
    - State Fair, 2007; CD-3890-2891
    - State Fair, 2009; CD-3906
  - H. Exhibits and Demonstrations
    - Clothing demo- Watertown, New York, exhibit- Allegheny County Fair, demonstration train exhibit- Ontario County, craft leaders- Delaware County, 1923, 1930, 1927, 1934 (Box 135, Folder 111)
    - Farm and Home Week exhibit- Roberts Hall, cover for brochure, organizational chart, 1930 (Box 135, Folder 112)
    - Club exhibits- Tompkins County, Chemung County, 1924, 1928 (Box 135, Folder 113)
    - Exhibits- various events, 1915-1920 (Box 135, Folder 114)
    - Exhibits- Erie County, Monroe County, 1920, 1923 (Box 135, Folder 115)
    - Exhibits - Otsego County, Oswego County, Chemung County, 1921, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 116)
    - Foods worker- Chemung County, foods worker exhibition, Date Unknown (Box 135, Folder 117)
    - Potato triating demo (Box 135, Folder 118)
    - Food preparation- Monroe County, Chemung County, 1924, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 119)
    - Exhibits, 1920-1929 (Box 140, Folder 53)
  - I. Canning
    - Canning- Tompkins County, Otsego County, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 120)
    - Chemung County, 1920, 1921, 1922 (Box 135, Folder 121)
    - Clothing club exhibit; 4-H club exhibit, Lawrence County; Girls 4-H Club Junior Field Days, 1935, 1927 (Box 136, Folder 24)
    - Calf sale- Schoharie County, 1919 (Box 136, Folder 25)
    - Judging cattle- Otsego County, 1919 (Box 136, Folder 26)
  - J. Various Subjects
    - Junior club members- International Livestock Exposition, 1919 (Box 143, Folder 5)
    - Publication - Junior Extension Work- "The Four-H Story", 1920-1929 (Box 135, Folder 122)
    - Room improvement program- Oneida County, Westinghouse Contest, 1936, 1945 (Box 135, Folder 123)
    - Farmers Week, 1920 (Box 135, Folder 124)
    - School lunch (Box 135, Folder 125)
    - Clothing worker- Allegheny County, clothing project- one Delaware County, one unnamed, Jefferson County, 1919, 1924 (Box 135, Folder 126)
    - Junior Field Days, 1924 (Box 137, Folder 2)
    - Junior Field Days, 1927 (Box 135, Folder 127)
    - Uniforms, group photo- Ottawa experimental farms- 4-H members St. Lawrence County, 1920-1929 (Box 135, Folder 128)
    - U.S.D.A. experimental farm- visit, 1931 (Box 143, Folder 9)
    - National Rural Electrification Contest state winners, 1943 (Box 135, Folder 129)
    - Style review- St. Lawrence County, style dress revue winner, 1937, 1931 (Box 135, Folder 130)
    - Uniforms- Dutchess County, 1926 (Box 135, Folder 131)
    - Style dress revue, 1937 (Box 135, Folder 132)
    - Children modeling clothes, Undated (Box 136, Folder 28)
    - Junior extension local leaders meeting with Mrs. Nevin, 1934-05 (Box 136, Folder 29)
    - South New Berlin 4-H Club district revue, 1940 (Box 136, Folder 30)
    - Sullivan county 4-H girls modeling clothes from feed bags, 1940 (Box 136, Folder 31)
    - 4-H members modeling garments made from sugar sacks at Mrs. Nevin's house, 1941 (Box 136, Folder 32)
    - Tompkin's county 4-h girls modeling wartime garments, 1942 (Box 136, Folder 33)
    - 4-H club conference, 1944-09-19-1944-09-20 (Box 136, Folder 34)
      Miss Frost instructor
    - New York State champions, 1941 (Box 135, Folder 133)
    - Camp photos (Box 135, Folder 134)
    - Unidentified photos and negatives (Box 135, Folder 135)
    - Food selection photo used for exhibit panels, 1925 (Box 136, Folder 27)
    - 4-H awards master farmer banquet in Willard Straight Hall, 1933 (Box 137, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural engineering (Box 138, Folder 1)
    - Agricultural engineering- electrical program (Box 138, Folder 2)
    - Agricultural engineering- power lawn equipment (Box 138, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural engineering- woodworking program (Box 138, Folder 4)
    - 4-H demonstrations (Box 138, Folder 5)
    - Dog care and training- animal science (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - Empire Farm Days- demonstrations (Box 138, Folder 7)
    - Exploring The Arts (Box 138, Folder 8)
    - Gardening projects (Box 138, Folder 9)
    - Indoor gardening projects (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - Housing and design projects (Box 138, Folder 11)
    - Entomology and projects with special needs children (Box 138, Folder 12)
    - Projects with young children (Box 138, Folder 13)
    - Conservation (Box 138, Folder 14)
    - Cooking (Box 138, Folder 15)
    - Camping and outdoor camping (Box 138, Folder 16)
    - 4-H mobile learning centers (Box 138, Folder 17)
    - Model Farm-Fresh Fund (Box 138, Folder 18)
    - Poultry science (Box 138, Folder 19)
    - Public speaking (Box 138, Folder 20)
    - Recognitions- awards (Box 138, Folder 21)
    - Sewing projects (Box 138, Folder 22)
    - Shooting sports (Box 138, Folder 23)
    - Leadership training (Box 138, Folder 24)
    - Staff training (Box 138, Folder 25)
    - Teen ambassador training (Box 138, Folder 26)
    - New York City 4-H, 1986 (Box 138, Folder 29)
    - New York State 4-H Club Foundation, 1973 (Box 138, Folder 30)
    - New York State 4-H Foundation trustees- New York City tour, 1987 (Box 138, Folder 31)
    - New York State 4-H leaders forum, 1977 (Box 138, Folder 39)
    - New York State 4-H leaders forum, 1981 (Box 138, Folder 40)
    - New York State 4-H leaders forum, 1981,1985 (Box 138, Folder 41)
    - Statewide personal development programs (Box 138, Folder 42)
    - State program- Mulligan Stew- includes program files (Box 138, Folder 43)
    - Albert Hoefee- New York State 4-H Club leader (Box 138, Folder 58)
    - Newspaper articles, 1978-1980 (Box 138, Folder 63)
    - Annual report, 1972-1973 (Box 138, Folder 64)
    - Fullager family at Penn Yan, 1945 (Box 138, Folder 65)
    - Various group photos, 1940-1979 (Box 138, Folder 66)
    - Catalog of 4-H films (Box 138, Folder 67)
    - Awards, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 1)
    - Awards- includes photo with Franklin Roosevelt (Box 139, Folder 2)
    - Awards, 1938-1942 (Box 139, Folder 3)
    - Awards, 1940-1949 (Box 139, Folder 4)
    - Scholarship winners, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 5)
    - National 4-H Club Congress- 25th anniversary scholarship recipients, 1946 (Box 139, Folder 6)
    - Membership signs, pins, brochures, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 7)
    - Membership signs- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 8)
    - Membership signs- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 9)
    - Leadership training- various counties, 1920-1929 (Box 139, Folder 10)
    - County boards and various committees, 1920-1949 (Box 139, Folder 11)
    - 1913 Model T car driven by Harold Hamilton, Ernest Rynph (Dutchess County) to short course at Cornell, 1930-1939 (Box 139, Folder 12)
    - Dutchess County staff -includes Marlene Baker, Elsie Berrie, Glenda Payne, no date (Box 143, Folder 14)
    - Slides of Tompkins County Youth Conference and Foxfire Conference, 1975 (Box 140, Folder 80)
    - 4-H members with Senator D'Amato, 1990-1999 (Box 143, Folder 12)
    - 4-H conference at Cornell, 2000 (Box 143, Folder 13)
    - CBS Morning Show, 2002-08-17 (Box 142)
    - Photos with Assemblyman Paul Tonko, 2002 (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - Photos with Governor Cuomo, 2012 (Box 146, Folder 42)
    - Teen ambassador retreat, career exploration, volunteer forum, 1997-2000 (Box 147)
    - Photos of various 4-H events, 2000-2018 (Box 148, Folder 56)
    - Forum images, Date Unknown; CD-3867-3868
    - Yates County photos, 1999-2000; CD-3900
    - Centennial, 2002; CD-3866
    - Foundation scholarship, 2004; CD-3887
    - Shooting Sports, 2004-2005; CD-3892
    - 4-H events, some images from downtown Ithaca, 2005; CD-3894
    - 4-H images from various forums, conferences, events, 2006-2008; CD-3863-3864
    - 4-H photographs used for publicity, 2006; CD-5006
    - 4-H Camp Bristol Hills STEM Camp, 2007; CD-3869
    - 4-H forestry, Arnot Forest, 2007-2008; CD-3897
    - 4-H Primitive Pursuits Program, 2008-05-22; CD-3898
    - New York State Fair 4-H fashion revue, 2008; CD-5007-5008
    - NYSACCE 4-H awards dinner, 2008-10-16; CD-3865
    - 4-H public presentations, 2002; CD-5004
    - New York State Fair 4-H dog show, 2012; CD-5010
    - Career Explorations, 2002; CD-3870
    - Career Explorations, 2003; CD-3871-3872
    - Career Explorations, 2004; CD-3873-3874, CD-3895-3896
    - Career Explorations, 2005; CD-3875-3876
    - Career Explorations, 2006; CD-3878-3882
    - Career Explorations, 2007; CD-3883-3886
    - Career Explorations, 2014-07-01-2014-07-03; CD-5009
- Series VI. Memorabilia and Ephemera
  - Scrapbook "A Country School Picnic at Cornell University", 1905-05-26 (Box 118)
  - Scrapbooks, 1936-1952 (Box 120)
  - 4-H club hat and armband (Box 143, Folder 52)
  - 4-H banner, 2001-09 (Box 143, Folder 53)
  - National 4-H Hall of Fame medal- Nancy Thayer, 2002-04-11 (Box 143, Folder 54)
  - National 4-H Hall of Fame medal- Liberty Hyde Bailey, 2003-04-04 (Box 143, Folder 54)
  - National 4-H Hall of Fame medal- Martha Van Rensselaer, 2004 (Box 143, Folder 54)
  - Pencil- New York State 4-H Clubs (Box 143)
  - 4-H beanie, MU-2751 (Box 148, Folder 57)